# CALEB HORNER

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

## CONTACT

(843) 452-6982
CHORNER79@GMAIL.COM
LINKEDIN - /CALEB-HORNER
GITHUB - /CMHORNER

# **PROFILE**

I am enthusiastic and enthralled with coding, thrilled with the prospect of each new avenue and learning experience. I will fit seamlessly into any great company culture and work to be both a leader and a quality team player. I have great passion for fun people, interesting projects and the pursuit of perfection.

## SKILLS

- Ruby on Rails
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- 5+ years Leadership
- Human Resources
- Creative Problem Solving
- Budget Management
- Focused, Enthusiastic Teamwork

## **EXPERIENCE**

industry standards

#### STUDENT, CODE IMMERSION PROGRAM

TECH TALENT SOUTH | AUG 2017 - OCT 2017

-Focus on Entry level understanding of multiple frontend and back-end programming languages including Html, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, with a focus on Ruby and Rails as a framework. At https://tradeappcmj.herokuapp.com/ there is a working example of one app, a simple stock app using an API and Devise.
 -Gained experience with AWS, API keys, Git and Heroku-Emphasis on problem-solving, decision-making and

#### MARKETING COORDINATOR/CUSTOMER SERVICE

QUEENSBORO SHIRT CO. | SEP 2016 - AUG 2017

- -Respond to customer issues rapidly by phone, online chat or email
  - -Contribute to online social media marketing campaign
  - -Manage all customer issues through Facebook campaign
  - -Create unique copy for email campaigns on a weekly basis

### FOOD AND BEVERAGE DIRECTOR/EXECUTIVE CHEF

HOLIDAY INN HISTORIC DOWNTOWN CHARLESTON | DEC 2013 - AUG 2016

- -Began as line cook in 2013, moved to Sous Chef and by 2014 was working as the Executive Chef and Food and Beverage Director of the hotel
  - -responsibilities covered all food and beverage related activities of the hotel, from rooms to amenities to restaurant
  - -responsible for all Human Resources within the restaurant
  - -developed all hiring, training and procedural SOPs for the restaurant
  - -responsible for inventory and budget of restaurant and bar. Managed to bring a restaurant that was running at a 42% food cost down to a 31%vfood cost in nearly 3 months and continually maintain similar numbers.
  - -worked to limit turnover and raise retention by modernizing our staff communication pipeline and kitchen operations

# **EDUCATION**

**ASSOCIATE OF ARTS** 

TRIDENT TECHNICAL COLLEGE. CHARLESTON, SC